[
	{ "question": "red", "answer": "あかい" },
	{ "question": "there is", "answer": "あります" },
	{ "question": "good", "answer": "いい" },
	{ "question": "pond", "answer": "いけ" },
	{ "question": "stone", "answer": "いし" },
	{ "question": "chair", "answer": "いす" },
	{ "question": "dog", "answer": "いぬ" },
	{ "question": "living room", "answer": "いま" },
	{ "question": "now", "answer": "いま" },
	{ "question": "there is", "answer": "います" },
	{ "question": "various", "answer": "いろいろ" },
	{ "question": "on (above)", "answer": "うえ" },
	{ "question": "rabbit", "answer": "うさぎ" },
	{ "question": "behind", "answer": "うしろ" },
	{ "question": "station", "answer": "えき" },
	{ "question": "a crowd of people", "answer": "おおぜい" },
	{ "question": "mother", "answer": "おかあさん" },
	{ "question": "turtle", "answer": "かめ" },
	{ "question": "cute", "answer": "かわいい" },
	{ "question": "tree", "answer": "き" },
	{ "question": "shoes", "answer": "くつ" },
	{ "question": "country", "answer": "くに" },
	{ "question": "car", "answer": "くるま" },
	{ "question": "black", "answer": "くろい" },
	{ "question": "entrance", "answer": "げんかん" },
	{ "question": "park", "answer": "こうえん" },
	{ "question": "child", "answer": "こども" },
	{ "question": "trash can", "answer": "ごみばこ" },
	{ "question": "fish", "answer": "さかな" },
	{ "question": "under", "answer": "した" },
	{ "question": "shirt", "answer": "シャツ" },
	{ "question": "good", "answer": "じょうぶ" },
	{ "question": "white", "answer": "しろい" },
	{ "question": "bedroom", "answer": "しんしつ" },
	{ "question": "aquarium", "answer": "すいぞくかん" },
	{ "question": "elephant", "answer": "ぞう" },
	{ "question": "beside", "answer": "そば" },
	{ "question": "nearby", "answer": "そば" },
	{ "question": "kitchen", "answer": "だいどころ" },
	{ "question": "a lot of", "answer": "たくさん" },
	{ "question": "building", "answer": "たてもの" },
	{ "question": "desk", "answer": "つくえ" },
	{ "question": "table", "answer": "テーブル" },
	{ "question": "television", "answer": "テレビ" },
	{ "question": "door", "answer": "ドア" },
	{ "question": "animal", "answer": "どうぶつ" },
	{ "question": "zoo", "answer": "どうぶつえん" },
	{ "question": "library", "answer": "としょかん" },
	{ "question": "next to", "answer": "となり" },
	{ "question": "which", "answer": "どの" },
	{ "question": "bird", "answer": "とり" },
	{ "question": "which", "answer": "どれ" },
	{ "question": "inside", "answer": "なか" },
	{ "question": "what", "answer": "なに" },
	{ "question": "garden", "answer": "にわ" },
	{ "question": "cat", "answer": "ねこ" },
	{ "question": "banana", "answer": "バナナ" },
	{ "question": "florist", "answer": "はなや" },
	{ "question": "panda", "answer": "パンダ" },
	{ "question": "drawer", "answer": "ひきだし" },
	{ "question": "person", "answer": "ひと" },
	{ "question": "open space", "answer": "ひろば" },
	{ "question": "pencil case", "answer": "ふでばこ" },
	{ "question": "bathroom", "answer": "ふろば" },
	{ "question": "bed", "answer": "ベッド" },
	{ "question": "bookshelf", "answer": "ほんだな" },
	{ "question": "bookstore", "answer": "ほんや" },
	{ "question": "in front of", "answer": "まえ" },
	{ "question": "window", "answer": "まど" },
	{ "question": "round", "answer": "まるい" },
	{ "question": "gate", "answer": "もん" },
	{ "question": "goat", "answer": "やぎ" },
	{ "question": "lion", "answer": "ライオン" },
	{ "question": "lisa", "answer": "リサ" },
	{ "question": "corridor", "answer": "ろうか" }
]
